{
    "id": "78cd04ab97d34cc2a6be0c03ece70b48",
    "title": "Phrasal Verbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The opposition called ........................... the resignation of the minister.",
            "description": "To call for is to demand.",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "out",
                "up"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Call ................................ the ambulance.",
            "description": "To call for something is to telephone for it.",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "for",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Emergency situations like these call ................................... swift action.",
            "description": "Call for can mean require. ",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "for",
                "out"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "We had to call ................................ a doctor because dad complained of uneasiness.",
            "description": "To call somebody in is to get them to pay a visit.",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "out",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "He has a short fuse but he calms ................................... fairly quickly.",
            "description": "To calm down is to stop being angry.",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "down",
                "out"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I don't care .............................. fish or meat. I eat veggies whenever possible.",
            "description": "To care for something is to like it.",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "for",
                "about"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She got carried ..................................... when she heard that she was the winner.",
            "description": "To get carried away is to get so emotional that you lose control.",
            "answers": [
                "off",
                "away",
                "over"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "They hoped that the new government would carry the infrastructure projects ....................................",
            "description": "To carry something forward is to make it progress. ",
            "answers": [
                "forward",
                "forth"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Our team carried ...................................... the first prize.",
            "description": "To carry off is to win.",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "off",
                "away"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The volunteers quietly carried .................................... with their work.",
            "description": "To carry on is to continue.",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "off",
                "away"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The party carried ................................ into the night.",
            "description": "Carry over can mean continue past a certain point.",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "over",
                "away"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "In spite of the opposition, the government carried .................................. the reforms.",
            "description": "To carry through is to complete successfully.",
            "answers": [
                "off",
                "through",
                "over"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}